Right now, begin to ask for the gift of eyes that see and ears that hear what Jesus is telling you.
Ask God to liberate your spirit.
Liberate my spirit.
Liberate my spirit, oh Lord.
Ears that hear what Jesus is telling me.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In Jesus Christ's name.
All those challenges are darkness.
Evil spirit is darkness.
Infirmity, setback, stagnation, sickness are darkness.
Say to yourself:
I will never forget the Light who liberated me when I come out of the darkness.
That infirmity is darkness; that evil spirit is darkness.
I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
You darkness in my life - right now, begin to separate yourself from that darkness.
Separate yourself from that darkness.
That infirmity is darkness; begin to separate yourself from that darkness!
I command all unclean spirits operating in your life - command them out, in the name of Jesus!
All unclean spirits operating in your life, business, career - command them out!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
In the mighty name of Jesus!
I command all unclean spirits operating in your life, career, marriage, business -
command them out!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
Watch the screen of your television.
In the mighty name of Jesus!
Don't forget: Unclean spirit is sickness, stagnation, setback, failure, infirmity.
Right now, take note of that.
All unclean spirits operating in your life, career, health, marriage,
I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Command them out!
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
You can see what is happening right now.
People are vomiting out the root cause of their problems
as the Spirit of God moves in the midst of the congregation
to expose all unclean spirits operating in the lives of the people -
the unclean spirits operating in their health, career, marriage, business
are being commanded out by the superior power of our Lord Jesus Christ.
Viewers around the world, join in the prayer and you too will be a partaker of this mighty anointing
as the Spirit of God is flushing people's systems and removing everything that is not from God in their lives.
We can see right here in the overflow congregation...
In the mighty name of Jesus!
Whatever satan and his cohort might have used to connect you, to connect your business,
whatever chain, whatever medium used to connect you to himself -
be broken, in the name of Jesus!
Begin to break it!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Break it!
In the name of Jesus!
Be it sickness - break it!
Break the chain!
Whatever satan might have used - satan can use sickness to connect you to himself,
satan can use failure - by the time you are facing failure, he is somewhere laughing, happy
because he wants to see you unhappy, depressed.
Listen to me once again when I say,
"Whatever satan might have used to connect you to himself".
Now, you begin to break that thing satan used -
those things satan is using to affect your joy.
You want to be happy.
Come on.
Viewers all over the world, begin to reason with yourself right now.
Reason with yourself - you will see what satan might have used.
You will see what satan is using to connect you to himself.
He wants you to be unhappy. He wants you to be sad.
He wants you to look at Jesus in a bad light.
Reason with yourself - you will see what satan is using to connect you to himself.
It can be sickness, infirmity, stagnation, nightmares, loneliness or depression.
These are the tools of satan.
Whatever satan might have been using to connect you to himself -
be broken, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Be broken, in the name of Jesus!
You want to be happy but when this pain, affliction, challenge, situation comes,
it changes your joy.
Be broken, in the name of Jesus!
When Jesus says, "Yes", no one can say, "No".
I can hear chains falling!
Chain of setback - I can hear chains falling!
Chain of stagnation - I can hear chains falling!
Chain of failure - I can hear chains falling!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
In the name of Jesus!
Rejoice!
Yes.
That chain of affliction is falling right now!
I can see them falling!
I can see them giving way, in the name of Jesus!
How much is your joy?
You will not leave here today without you being restored.
That your health - be examined, in the name of Jesus!
Your blood - be examined, in the name of Jesus!
Your kidneys - be examined, in the name of Jesus!
Your liver - be examined, in the name of Jesus!
Your bones - be examined, in the name of Jesus!
You affliction - be ceased!
In the blood - be ceased!
In the kidneys - be ceased!
In the liver - be ceased!
Wherever it is located, you affliction -
in the blood, kidneys, bones -
you affliction - say, out!
Place your hand.
If you have loved ones somewhere, stretch your hand.
Place your hand wherever that affliction is.
Your loved one - stretch your hand forward.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Whatever hinders my healing - give way!
Whatever hinders my deliverance - give way!
In the name of Jesus!
Whatever hinders your deliverance - give way!
Say, give way!
Be it your weakness, doubt - I say, give way!
Where can you go from His presence?
[Nowhere.]
Your Helper is coming!
Our Helper is coming!
He is coming to you!
He is coming to me!
My Helper is coming to me!
He is coming to me to restore my kidneys, liver, bones, blood!
Wherever it is located - my Helper is coming, in the name of Jesus!
I can't hear you. In the name of Jesus!
[Amen!]
Woman Previously Booked For Operation
Delivers Baby Safely During Mass Prayer
Watch the screen of your television - you can see what is happening live here at The SCOAN.
A lady has just delivered a beautiful baby in the presence of God.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Woman Previously Booked For Operation
Delivers Baby Safely During Mass Prayer
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
God is talking to you.
It is a sign.
What you are seeing is a sign that your business has been delivered!
Your career has been delivered!
Healed Of Difficulty In Walking
No Longer Using A Crutch
Your health has been delivered!
Your beautiful future has been delivered!
Tell your neighbour, "It is a sign".
[It is a sign.]
It is a sign to me that my career has been delivered!
It is a sign to me that my business has been delivered!
It is a sign to me that my finances have been delivered!
It is a sign to me that my destiny has been delivered!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Hallelujah.
If you know that the Lord has done it for you, let me see!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Overflow Congregation
He has done it for you, in Jesus' name.
Yes, whatever you have as a contact for your nation.
God's intervention!
Right now, begin to invite God to your country, nation.
God's intervention in your economy!
God's intervention in your political issue!
God's intervention!
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
I can't hear you.
[Amen.]
Again and again.
Prayer For The Nations
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Don't forget your assignment - assignment from God.
Business of meditation.
At your level, we should not deceive ourselves.
Whom are you praying to?
Lay the foundation.
Our heart is divided; there is a conflict between the flesh and spirit.
Create room, a home for the Holy Ghost by meditation.
Meditation brings revelation.
Right now, begin to constantly praise His holy name in your heart.
Pray, sing hymns, spiritual songs, melodies in your heart to the Lord, all the time; day and night.
That is the best prayer that will lead you to the Holy Ghost.
Now, you need a visit of the Holy Ghost.
Invite Him.
You need to know the God you are talking to, you are praying to.
When you pray to God, you hear from Him.
It is two way.
- "Good Morning, Sir."
- "Good morning, my son."
But for so long, you keep praying and you don't hear from Him.
Each time you talk to Him, you must hear.
Hallelujah.
Right now, open your lips and say after me...
Remember our message today.
Not just confessing but believe.
Whatever you say right now, live by it.
Lord Jesus, come into my heart.
Wash me with Your precious blood.
Lord Jesus, make me Your channel, Your channel of love where there is hate.
Make me Your channel - Your channel of shining light where there is darkness.
Make me Your channel - Your channel of forgiveness where there is sin, wrong or mistake.
Make me Your channel of forgiveness.
Lord Jesus, make me Your channel of pardon where there is injury.
In Jesus Christ's name.
[Amen.]
The SCOAN Sunday Service
My name is Mrs Eze Juilet. I'm from Enugu State (Nigeria).
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was that I was booked for an operation
due to the cord that was wrapped around my baby's neck.
I was not able to deliver my baby without an operation because of the cord.
During the Mass Prayer, I was in the Overflow Section of the Church.
When the man of God was praying, I fell into labour and my water burst.
They rushed to help me and I delivered my baby successfully without any operation.
Hallelujah! Clap for Jesus Christ!
Glory be to God. So you have heard it from the woman
that she delivered her baby instantly without any operation.
Madam, can you tell us the sex of your baby?
He's a bouncing baby boy.
Let us put our hands together for Jesus!
Could you introduce to us the man sitting beside you, madam?
He's my lovely husband.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Thank You, Jesus!
All I have to say is "Thank You, Jesus" because it was a long journey.
This baby had been giving signs to come out but no way.
During the Mass Prayer, I was upstairs praying.
Even my prayer request, I wrote about her alone - her name alone.
I said, "God of Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua, you have been doing it for others.
My own will never be different".
So I was surprised, during the Mass Prayer, I glanced to the TV.
I now saw her clothes.
I was amazed and said, "Is it not my wife?"
I was shocked; I screamed.
I told everyone around me, "She is my wife!"
And how do you feel, now that you are a father of a new-born baby?
If you can view me properly, you will know that I am still vibrating.
I don't know what to say. Thank You, Jesus!
TT: Mel Flowers 26/01/2019
RV ROBERT BEGIER 06/02/2019